<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cebu Home Pages</title>
    <description>Cebu Home Page, helping you buy and sell your property with ease.</description>
    <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/mob/ia.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <updated>2017-10-19T09:55:16+08:00</updated>
    <id></id>
    <author>
      <name></name>
    </author>
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandani Bay launches impressive show gallery</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-03-sunstar-mandani-bay-launches-impressive-show-gallery/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-03-sunstar-mandani-bay-launches-impressive-show-gallery/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>MANDANI Bay, a joint venture of Hongkong Land and Taft Properties, brings Cebu closer to becoming one of the world’s famous waterfront destinations, soon joining such icons as the Thames...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-03-sunstar-mandani-bay-launches-impressive-show-gallery/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Mandani Bay launches impressive show gallery</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg" />
        <figcaption>Mandani Bay</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:10:00 +08">2016-11-01 17:10:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
  MANDANI Bay, a joint venture of Hongkong Land and Taft Properties, brings Cebu closer to becoming one of the world’s famous waterfront destinations, soon joining such icons as the Thames River in London, Manhattan in New York, the Sydney Harbour, Victoria Harbour in Hongkong, and the Marina Bay in Singapore.


</p>
  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://weekend.sunstar.com.ph/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/mandani-bay.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   (From left) Taft Properties Chairman Jack Gaisano, Taft Properties Chief Marketing Officer Ryan Villaflores, Mandani Bay Project Director Gilbert Ang, outgoing mayor and Sixth District Representative-elect Jonas Cortes, outgoing sixth district representative and Mandaue City Mayor-elect Luigi Quisumbing, Taft Properties Chief Operating Officer Christopher Narciso, Chief Representative of Hongkong Land in the Philippines Finn Carew, and Vicsal Holdings Co. Group President and Chief Operating Officer Christopher Beshouri
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<p>
Located along the Mactan Channel, the 20-hectare waterfront was launched last May 19 in a spectacular affair that celebrated Cebuano culture and creativity whilst giving guests a glimpse of the world-class lifestyle destination that will put Mandaue City and Cebu on the global map.

 </p>

<p>The program showcased award-winning Cebuano performers such as the Mandaue Children’s Choir, the Cebu Classic Youth Orchestra, the University of Cebu Dance Company and Soprano Windey Prado, and was capped off by fireworks and a ceremony to formally open the doors to its 1,500-square-meter show gallery, the finest in the country and the first structure to rise at Mandani Bay.
</p>
<p>
Cutting the ribbon were Chief Representative of Hongkong Land in the Philippines Finn Carew, Taft Properties Chief Operating Officer Christopher Narciso, Taft Properties Chairman Jack Gaisano, Hongkong Land Executive Director Robert Wong, then Sixth District Representative and Mandaue City Mayor-elect Luigi Quisumbing, Mandaue City Vice Mayor-elect Carlo Fortuna, and Cebu Vice Gov. Agnes Magpale. Also in attendance was then Mandaue City Mayor and Sixth District Representative-elect Jonas Cortes and Cordova Mayor Adelino Sitoy. The recently crowned Miss Mandaue 2016 Malka Shaver and Second Runner-up Luzenne Jones also graced the event.
</p>
<p>
  A fusion of the quaint Cebu cityscape and the international landscape, Mandani Bay transforms Mandaue into a contemporary yet culturally and environmentally sensitive lifestyle destination. Seeing the rapid economic and population boom in Cebu, Narciso said that residential demands remain robust across different sectors. Moreover, he added that Mandani Bay is also a product of personal dreams and a vision of bringing into Cebu a world-class development it deserves. Taking into account the environmental aspect of the project, Carew said that in this time of exponential population growth, 

</p>
<blockquote>“vertical is the way to go for a sustainable development.”</blockquote>
<p>With environmental touches, expansive green attributes, and natural aesthetic, the 130-billion project provides a conducive environment, finest infrastructure, and state-of-the-art features and amenities for leisure and outdoor activity.</p>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://weekend.sunstar.com.ph/blog/2016/07/03/mandani-bay-launches-impressive-show-gallery/"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandani Bay Suites Phase 1</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/mandani-bay-suites/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/mandani-bay-suites/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>The waterfront lifestyle at Mandani Bay begins at Mandani Bay Suites, the property’s first residential enclave. Two towers are situated on a large podium that houses recreational amenities, community support...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/mandani-bay-suites/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Mandani Bay Suites Phase 1</h1>
                      
      <!-- The header image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure data-mode=aspect-fit>
      <video loop>
        
        <source src="http://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/vid/mb-flythrough.mp4" type="video/mov" />
     
        </video>
      </figure>
      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-04 18:00:00 +08">2016-11-04 18:00:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
  The waterfront lifestyle at Mandani Bay begins at Mandani Bay Suites, the property’s first residential enclave.
</p>
<p>
Two towers are situated on a large podium that houses recreational amenities, community support facilities, and car parks. </p>

<p>Mandani Bay Suites features studio to three-bedroom units, and a number of individually designed special units including townhouses, lofts, penthouses, and garden units. Aptly names for its luxurious fusion of convenience and exclusivity, this landmark gleams with a modern yet timeless exterior.
</p>
<p>
Whether your passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.

</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/mbs.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-extra-large">Twin Towers of Mandani Bay Suites</h1> 
   eatures studio to three-bedroom units, and a number of individually designed special units including townhouses, lofts, penthouses, and garden units.
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandani Bay opens world-class Show Gallery</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-31-thestandard-mandani-bay-opens-world-class-show-gallery/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-31-thestandard-mandani-bay-opens-world-class-show-gallery/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>Taft Property Venture Development Corp., the real estate arm of the Metro Gaisano Group, together with international property investment, management and development group Hongkong Land will transform Cebu into a...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-31-thestandard-mandani-bay-opens-world-class-show-gallery/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Mandani Bay opens world-class Show Gallery</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/marina-1.jpg" />
        <figcaption>The Marina</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:00:01 +08">2016-11-01 17:00:01 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
 Taft Property Venture Development Corp., the real estate arm of the Metro Gaisano Group, together with international property investment, management and development group Hongkong Land will transform Cebu into a global  waterfront destination with the opening of the 1,500-square-meter show gallery for Mandani Bay, the multi-billion peso 20-hectare waterfront township property that will rise in Mandaue City.</p>
 <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/The_20-hectare_waterfront_development_is_located_along_the_Mactan_Channel_in_Mandaue_City.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>The 20-hectare waterfront development is located along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

 <p>
The Mandani Bay Show Gallery located at F.E. Zuellig Avenue marks the first completed structure in the entire waterfront township. The developer’s first residential property, Mandani Bay Suites, is slated to finish by 2020 and the full-scale exhibition area is already open for interested buyers. The gallery showcases an experiential display of the scale models of the entire waterfront property as well as the showroom for the studios and units that are available for buyers. 
</p>

<figure class="op-slideshow">


<figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/Mandani_Bay_project_director_Gilber_Ang.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class="op-vertical-bottom"> 1/2 </h1> Mandani Bay project director Gilbert Ang
    <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Gilbert Ang</cite> </figcaption>

 </figure>

 <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/Hongkong_Land_chief_representative_for_the_Philippines_Finn_Carew_and_Taft_Properties_chief_operating_officer_Christopher_Narciso.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class="op-vertical-bottom"> 2/2 </h1> Hongkong Land chief representative for the Philippines Finn Carew and Taft Properties chief operating officer Christopher Narciso
    <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Finn Carew + Christopher Narciso</cite> </figcaption>

 </figure>
 </figure>

<p>
The projected completion for the whole township project is in 15 years in anticipation that all factors of the development will go as planned. Eight phases will be implemented towards completion and 80 percent of the entire property will be for residential use. A total of 25 towers are expected to rise around it, with expansive podium blocks interconnected by footbridges that will connect residents to all the amenities within the property as well as the retail and activity spaces. 
</p>
 <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/Manadani_Bay_Suites%2C_the_first_residential_area_for_Mandani_Bay.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>Manadani Bay Suites scale model can be seen in the newly opene Show Gallery
</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

<p>
During the launch of the Show Gallery last May 19, the Gaisano family celebrated with the partner developers and all the people involved in the project together with Cebuanos who gathered at the exclusive event to witness the festivity auguring the rise of Mandani Bay. 
</p>
<blockquote>
  “We strongly feel that the residential demand in Cebu will remain robust,” says Taft Properties chief operating officer Christopher Narciso. According to Narciso, the current developments and lifestyle advancements in Cebu and the development of the property is promising for the Cebuanos and the local economy. 
</blockquote>

 <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/The_entire_propety_is_expected_to_finish_within_15_years.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>The entire property is expected to finish within 15 years
</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
 <blockquote>
   “In the last couple of years, Cebu has been able to achieve higher GDP growth than the national average,” he explains. “Taft Properties, being the local developer here in the last five years, has experienced very strong demand in terms of residential development.”
 </blockquote>

<p>
He adds that given the fundamentals of the Cebu economics, the country, the potential tourism boom and all the infrastructure that’s being put up in Cebu province including the rise of Mandani Bay show a lot of promise.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://thestandard.com.ph/panel/_files/image/Mandani_Bay_Suites.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>Artist's rendition of Mandani Bay Suites
</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

<p>The joint development venture of Hongkong Land with Taft Properties is by far the biggest property project of the international firm in the Philippines. In Manila, the developer currently has an existing partnership with Ayala Land Inc. for the development of Roxas Land Corp., soon to rise at the former location of Mandarin Hotel in Makati. </p>


 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://thestandard.com.ph/lifestyle/home-living/207029/mandani-bay-opens-world-class-show-gallery.html"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Water transport system</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-23-sunstar-water-transport-system/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-23-sunstar-water-transport-system/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>THE developer of a waterfront project in Mandaue City has expressed interest to coordinate with the government on a possible ferry transport system to operate in the area. Taft Property...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-23-sunstar-water-transport-system/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Water transport system</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/marina-1.jpg" />
        <figcaption>The Marina</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 18:00:00 +08">2016-11-01 18:00:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
THE developer of a waterfront project in Mandaue City has expressed interest to coordinate with the government on a possible ferry transport system to operate in the area.
</p>

<p>Taft Property Venture Development Corp. president Christopher Narciso said Mandani Bay in the North Reclamation Area can support such a development.</p>
<blockquote>
“We have been coordinating with them (government) regarding provisions for a marina along our waterfront, a ferry transport to traverse (Mactan Island to Cebu),”</blockquote>
<p>
Narciso told reporters at the grand launch of its 1,500-square-meter Mandani Bay show gallery last week.</p>
<p>
As traffic worsens in Mandaue City with the influx of vehicles to and from the cities of Cebu, Mandaue, and Lapu-Lapu, a ferry transport system would be a viable alternative.
Since last week, drivers and commuters complained about the heavy traffic on the two bridges linking Mactan and Mandaue.


 </p>
 <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/sites/default/files/field/image/article/mactan_16.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
      <h1>Traffic Solution</h1>
      With more vehicles on the roads, Taft Property Venture Development Corp. president Christopher Narciso is supporting the operation of a ferry transport system at the waterfront area of their Mandani Bay project ialong the Mandaue side of the Mactan Channel. 
    <cite>(Sun.Star Photo/Amper Campaña)</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<blockquote>
“We can’t say with certainty (when)..but we are committed to support it,” Narciso said. Asked if this will be a public private partnership (PPP), he said this will depend on the decision of the authorities.</blockquote>
<p>
Mandani Bay, a joint venture project of Taft Properties and Hongkong Land, takes inspiration from to world-class waterfront destinations like the Thames River in London, Manhattan in New York, the Sydney Harbour, Victoria Harbour in Hong Kong, and the Marina Bay in Singapore.</p>
<p>
The project is envisioned to transform Mandaue City into a premium lifestyle destination.
The waterfront development will occupy a 20-hectare lot and will be developed in eight phases. It is composed of 25 towers, 80 percent of which is for residential use.</p>
<p>
The rest will be for commercial and retail functions.
Hongkong Land Philippines chief representative Finn Carew said it may take them 15 years to compelete the entire development.</p>
<p>
In this phase of transition in government, Carew said condominium sales have not been affected. </p>
<blockquote>“Sales take up has been very strong, despite this time of change,” he said. Most of the buyers are Cebuano families.</blockquote>
<p>
Condomium units at Mandani Bay are currently sold at P2.8 million up to P28 million each.
</p>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://www.sunstar.com.ph/cebu/business/2016/05/23/water-transport-system-475343"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Master Plan</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/masterplan/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/masterplan/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>Strategically located along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City, Mandani Bay is a world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape. World Class Destination...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/masterplan/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>The Master Plan</h1>
                      
      <!-- The header image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure data-mode=aspect-fit>
      <video loop>
        
        <source src="http://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/vid/mb-flythrough.mp4" type="video/mov" />
     
        </video>
      </figure>
      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 18:00:00 +08">2016-11-01 18:00:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>Strategically located along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City, Mandani Bay is a world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-extra-large">World Class Destination</h1> 
   world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape.
    <cite>Marina</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<p>Built around a lifestyle of connectivity, this premium mixed-use community hosts a series of expansive podium blocks interconnected by footbridges. Residential towers rise from each of the podiums' amenity roof decks, whilst street front retail thrives along the wide boulevards.</p>
                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Urban Transformation - A Deeper Look at Mandani Bay</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-06-cebudailynews-an-urban-transformation-a-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-06-cebudailynews-an-urban-transformation-a-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>EVERY beloved place has a story, each full of monumental events that ultimately brought them to the progress they are embracing now. Transformations came about through innovative collaborations of several...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-06-cebudailynews-an-urban-transformation-a-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>An Urban Transformation - A Deeper Look at Mandani Bay</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
        <figcaption>mandani bay masterplan</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:00:01 +08">2016-11-01 17:00:01 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
 EVERY beloved place has a story, each full of monumental events that ultimately brought them to the progress they are embracing now.</p><p>
Transformations came about through innovative collaborations of several brilliant minds.</p><p>
This is how the visionary partnership between Taft Properties and Hongkong Land is set out to accomplish in Cebu: a transformation that brings out a distinctively defined lifestyle. The resulting project of this joint venture is the  premium mixed-used development Mandani Bay.
</p><p>
Cebu is rich in history, and this is the start of the Mandani Bay narrative. There is a parallelism among places that started out as discoveries by European explorers, just like Manhattan, and Sydney, and most other urban destinations in the world. In the 1500s, Venetian scholar Antonio Pigafetta noted in a written account of a settlement called “Mandani”, known today as Mandaue. The developers want to go back to this rich chapter of our history as an homage to how progress first touched our land.
Every corner of the Mandani Bay master plan embodies a plush, aesthetic sensibility that inspires imagination, creation, and innovation. Expansive podium blocks are interconnected by footbridges. From the amenity roof decks of each of these podiums rise residential towers, while wide boulevards host street-front retail. FSpanning on 20 hectares of land, it lays majestic on a waterfront along the Mactan
</p><p>
Channel in Mandaue City, providing a stunning view of the coast and encompassing city scape.
The location plays a big role in the progressive transformation Mandani Bay brings. With half of its side facing the water, it adds this essential element of life to our lifestyle, making it more magical, in a much more splendid way than anywhere else in the country. A 500-meter boardwalk is provisioned for one to enjoy a relaxing evening walk amidst a spectacular view of the Mactan Channel.  Mandani</p><p>
Bay’s spirited environment is filled with avenues bursting with new experiences waiting to be discovered every day.</p><p>
Mandani Bay also transforms individuals in their very core, inspiring a new kind of metropolitan lifestyle that is only possible in a progressive seaside township.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://cebudailynews.inquirer.net/files/2016/09/2-Mandani-Bay-skyline.png"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://cebudailynews.inquirer.net/104229/an-urban-transformation-a-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay#ixzz4JWzG5eHk"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LIVE YOUR PASSION</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>Strategically located along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City, Mandani Bay is a world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape. World Class Destination...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>LIVE YOUR PASSION</h1>
                      
      <!-- The header image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure data-mode=aspect-fit>
      <video loop>
        
        <source src="http://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/vid/mb-jingle.webm" type="video/webm" />
     
        </video>
      </figure>
      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-05 23:00:00 +08">2016-11-05 23:00:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>Strategically located along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City, Mandani Bay is a world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-extra-large">World Class Destination</h1> 
   world-class 20-hectare waterfront development with a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape.
    <cite>Marina</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<p>Built around a lifestyle of connectivity, this premium mixed-use community hosts a series of expansive podium blocks interconnected by footbridges. Residential towers rise from each of the podiums' amenity roof decks, whilst street front retail thrives along the wide boulevards.</p>
    
<p>At the base, the buildings are also connected by a system of exclusive parking spaces weaving throughout the property. For strolling aboveground or driving and parking underground, Mandani Bay provides complete convenience allowing time for loftier pursuits.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/marina-1.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-extra-large">Waterfront and Boardwalk</h1> 
   the Waterfront and Boardwalk emphasize Mandani Bay's extensive water anterior and serves as the highlight of this spectacular landmark.
    <cite>Marina</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

<p>A 500-meter water frontage defines this lifestyle destination, where the Boardwalk is always nearby to enable relaxation or an evening walk amidst a spectacular view of the Mactan Channel.</p>

<p>At the heart of Mandani Bay is the Green Promenade, a wide tree-lined avenue that cuts through the centre of the property, lending the environment a refreshing spirit that encourages an active lifestyle amongst residents.</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/footbridge-1.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-extra-large">Green Promendade and Footbridges</h1> 
   Interconnecting the tower podiums throughout the property, footbridges provide for easy and convenient conveyance from one point to another.
    <cite>Footbridges</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

<p>Mandani Bay has set the bar for a new era of development in the Philippines.</p>

<h1> The Story </h1>

<p>Arriving in Cebu in the 1500s with Portuguese explorer Ferdinand Magellan, Antonio Pigafetta, a Venetian scholar, writes in his book, “First Voyage Around the World”, of a chieftain named Apo Noan from a settlement called ‘Mandani’, known today as Mandaue. Inspired by this rich chapter of Cebu’s history, Mandaue’s premier modern community embraces its storied past as it looks to the future.</p>

  <!-- Photo with caption -->

    <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">

      <img src="http://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/magellan.jpg" />
       <figcaption><h1>First Voyage Around the World</h1>Arriving in Cebu in the 1500s with Portuguese explorer Ferdinand Magellan, Antonio Pigafetta, a Venetian scholar, writes in his book, “First Voyage Around the World”, of a chieftain named Apo Noan from a settlement called ‘Mandani’, known today as Mandaue.
                <cite>Mandaue is Mandani</cite>
            </figcaption>
                  </figure>
    

<h1> The Location </h1>      
<p>With Cebu in the center of the Philippines, and the Philippines at the center of the Asia-Pacific region, its location is a strategic jump off point to all points in the region. Which also explains why Cebu has always played a vital role in trade and commerce in Asia, even before its colonisation by Spain.</p>
<p>On the east of Mandani Bay, a scenic stretch of wharfs rolls out onto a broad view of the Osmeña Bridge and the urban scenery beyond. To the west, the development will have easy access to Cebu Business Park and Cebu City</p>

<figure class="op-map">
    <figcaption><h1>At the Heart of Mandaue City</h1>The future developments of Mandaue is bright.
            
            </figcaption>
      <script type="application/json" class="op-geotag">  
        {
          "type": "Feature",
          "geometry": 
            {
              "type": "Point",
              "coordinates": [ [10.320653, 123.936760], [10.320653, 123.936760] ]    
            },    
          "properties": 
            {      
              "title": "F.E. Zuellig Ave, Mandaue City, Cebu, Philippines",      
              "radius": 20,      
              "pivot": true,      
              "style": "satellite",
            }
        }  
      </script>
    </figure>

<h1> The Developers </h1>      
<p>Beyond the vision for Mandani Bay is the powerhouse partnership of Hongkong Land and Taft Properties.</p>

<h2>Hongkong Land</h2>
<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">

      <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/Hongkong_Land_Logo.png" />
       <figcaption><h1>Photograph Example</h1>Tap this image to make it expand. Tilt the phone right and left and see what happens.
                <cite>tunart/Getty Images</cite>
            </figcaption>
                  </figure>

<!-- Slideshow with multiple captions-->
<p>Hongkong Land is a listed leading property investment, management, and development group. The Group owns and manages almost 800,000 sq. m. of prime office and luxury retail property in key Asian cities, principally in Hong Kong and Singapore. Its Hong Kong Central portfolio represents some 450,000 sq. m. of prime property. It has a further 165,000 sq. m. of prestigious office space in Singapore mainly held through joint ventures, and a 50% interest in a leading office complex in Central Jakarta.</p>

<h2>Taft Properties</h2>
<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">

      <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/Taft_Logo.png" />
       <figcaption><h1>Photograph Example</h1>Tap this image to make it expand. Tilt the phone right and left and see what happens.
                <cite>tunart/Getty Images</cite>
            </figcaption>
                  </figure>

<!-- Slideshow with multiple captions-->
<p>Steadily rising to become one of the leading real estate developers in the Philippines, Taft Properties is changing the way we live by developing masterfully planned communities for young professionals, entrepreneurs, families, and retirees from here and abroad.</p>

<h2> The Best and Brightest </h2>
<figure class="op-slideshow">


<figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/Crone_Stacked.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class="op-vertical-bottom"> 1/8 </h1> Crone is a global architectural firm with head office based in Sydney, Australia.
    <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Crone/Master Planner</cite> </figcaption>

 </figure>
  
  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/architect_lwkpartners.jpg" />
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class=op-vertical-bottom> 2/8 </h1> LWK and Partners (HK) Limited (hereinafter referred to as “LWK”) is a multinational architectural practice with over 500 staff, providing architectural services through its offices in Hong Kong, Shenzhen, Shanghai, Guangzhou and Shenyang. 
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">LWK/Concept Planner</cite>
                </figcaption>
  </figure>
  
  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/aidea.jpg" />
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class="op-vertical-bottom"> 3/8 </h1> Aidea is one of the Philippine’s most recognized and highly ranked architectural practices in the world today. 
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Aidea/Concept Planner</cite>
                </figcaption>
                </figure>

  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/PTang_Logo.png" />
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
   <h1 class=op-vertical-bottom> 4/8 </h1> Ptang Studio was established in 1997 aand engages in diverse scope of projects.
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Ptang Studio/Interior Designer </cite>
            </figcaption>
  </figure>

  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/COEN_logo.jpg" />
   <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class=op-vertical-bottom> 5/8 </h1> Coen is a landscape architectural practice based in Singapore.
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Coen/Landscape Architect</cite>
                </figcaption>
  </figure>

   <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/CallisonRTKL-Logo.png" />
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
   <h1 class=op-vertical-bottom> 6/8 </h1> CallisonRTKL combines the legacy of two great design practices into an even stronger, more distinct voice that is characterized by the strength of our ideas, the spirit of our culture and the passion of our people to make the world a better place.
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">CallisonRTKL/Retail Architect</cite>
            </figcaption>
  </figure>
<figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/A-Bicol.png"/>
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class="op-vertical-bottom"> 7/8 </h1> Alberto Bicol Consulting Inc. is a consulting firm with large local and international experience.
    <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">A Bicol/Environmental Consultant</cite> </figcaption>

 </figure>
  
  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes,fb:comments">
    <img src="http://mandanibay.com/images/developers/parsons-brinckerhoff-logo.png" />
    <figcaption class="op-vertical-bottom">
      <h1 class=op-vertical-bottom> 8/8 </h1> Parsons Brinkerhoff is one of the world’s leading engineering professional services consulting firm.
                <cite class="op-vertical-bottom">Parsons Brinkerhoff/Traffic Consultant</cite>
                </figcaption>
  </figure>
  

  <figcaption>
    <h1>The Project Team</h1>
Some of the world’s most awarded architects, planners, and consultants have come together to create Mandani Bay.
  </figcaption>

  </figure>


  <h1>What's Next?</h1>
<p>Get to know more about Mandani. </p>
  <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Learn more about Mandani Bay">
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>You can also add a related articles element in the footer. Scroll down to the bottom of the story to see that feature in action.</p>

<h1>Here to help</h1>
<p>We can help you go through the buying process. We understand that you are a first time buyer and you may have done some research on how to purchase that property .. and you’d just like to have that thought verified.</p>
<p>
We can help you have a deeper understanding on how real estate buying works. You can connect with me now through <a href="tel:+639176312463">+639176312463 (direct line)</a> or facebook or <a href="mailto:luchelle@cebuhomepages.com">email</a>. It’s now easier than ever.</p>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deeper look at Mandani Bay</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-07-sunstar-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-07-sunstar-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>The visionary partnership between Taft Properties and Hongkong Land is set out to accomplish a transformation in Cebu that brings out a distinctively defined lifestyle. The resulting project of this...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-09-07-sunstar-deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Deeper look at Mandani Bay</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg" />
        <figcaption>video/mov</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:01:00 +08">2016-11-01 17:01:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
  The visionary partnership between Taft Properties and Hongkong Land is set out to accomplish a transformation in Cebu that brings out a distinctively defined lifestyle. The resulting project of this joint venture is the much talked-about, premium mixed-use development Mandani Bay.
</p>
<p>
Cebu is rich in history, and this is the start of the Mandani Bay narrative. There is a parallelism among places that started out as discoveries by European explorers, just like Manhattan and Sydney, and most other urban destinations in the world. </p>

<p>How do the brilliant minds that make up Taft Properties and Hongkong Land see Mandani Bay take us to this new era of progress? They do this, of course, by transforming a city, a physical transformation that births a new way of life.
</p>
<p>
Every corner of the Mandani Bay master plan embodies a plush, aesthetic sensibility that inspires imagination, creation and innovation. Expansive podium blocks are interconnected by footbridges.
</p>

<p>
  From a distance, Mandani Bay is a glittering metropolitan wonder. Spanning 20 hectares of land, it lies majestic on a waterfront along the Mactan Channel in Mandaue City, providing a stunning view of the coast and encompassing cityscape.
</p>

<p>
  With the marriage of land and sea prominent at Mandani Bay, another aspect of the progressive lifestyle is tapped into, one that is for adventure. One may bike around, climb walls, or conquer the water—whatever the spirit desires.
</p>

<p>
  In essence, Mandani Bay is a project that not just physically transforms Cebu not just into a bigger metropolitan giant, but also transforms individuals in their very core, inspiring a new kind of metropolitan lifestyle that is only possible in a progressive seaside township such as Mandani Bay.
</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://specials.sunstar.com.ph/communitynews/files/2016/09/Image142502.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://specials.sunstar.com.ph/communitynews/2016/09/07/deeper-look-at-mandani-bay/"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bayside living breaks new ground at Mandani Bay</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-02-philstar-bayside-living-breaks-new-ground-mandani-bay/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-02-philstar-bayside-living-breaks-new-ground-mandani-bay/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>MANILA, Philippines - Singapore has its Marina Bay while Hong Kong has the Victoria Harbor, the San Francisco Bay Area for Northern California, and the Hudson River for New York....</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-07-02-philstar-bayside-living-breaks-new-ground-mandani-bay/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Bayside living breaks new ground at Mandani Bay</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg" />
        <figcaption>Mandani Bay</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:00:10 +08">2016-11-01 17:00:10 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
  MANILA, Philippines - Singapore has its Marina Bay while Hong Kong has the Victoria Harbor, the San Francisco Bay Area for Northern California, and the Hudson River for New York. When it comes to landmark developments in progressive international cities, it has been real estate golden rule to build near the water. Other than serving as natural harbors, bays have the strategic advantage of having the best of both worlds: the tranquil view and embrace of the open water and a sweeping coastline that could command prime property prices. And, soon enough, Cebu’s key industrial city of Mandaue could take its place among the world’s most breathtaking bayside developments.


</p>
  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://media.philstar.com/images/the-philippine-star/lifestyle/modern-living/20160702/bayside-2.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   The Mandani Blue Seas’ two-bedroom loft unit elevates condominium living with higher ceiling, grander living areas, and utmost privacy, inspiring Cebu’s emergent homeowners to define domesticity in their own design.
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<p>
Found at the center of Opon Channel, the slender body of water that separates the island of Mactan from the Cebu mainland, Mandani Bay is a 20-hectare waterfront township dreamed up by the Gaisano Group’s Taft Properties in partnership with one of Asia’s leading property investment and development groups, Hong Kong Land. “If you believe in feng shui, this place has the best feng shui in Cebu. No wonder, among the portfolio that we have, Hong Kong Land CEO Robert Wong chose this one and no other. In your back, the mountain, in the front is the sea, and it is facing east,” describes Taft Properties’ chairman Jack Gaisano.



 </p>
 <blockquote>“I didn’t believe it could happen, but it happened. This is combining the international experience of Hong Kong Land, our local knowledge of the business in the Philippines, to develop the premier mixed-use development that will transform Cebu into a world-class lifestyle destination,” Gaisano assures.</blockquote>

<p>But while the 130-billion peso, 10,000-unit master-planned township development is poised to change the Mandaue City skyline in a fast decade and a half, the developers of Mandani Bay are also facing the challenges of a city in rapid flux. Riddled with metropolitan congestion, newer developments left and right, and the environmental impact of an expanding economy, the city of Mandaue certainly has a lot to live up for. “It is a city that is growing in terms of population that you have to go vertical. It’s the only way that the city develops sustainably,” observes Finn Carew, the chief representative of Hong Kong Land in the country.
</p>
<blockquote>“The vision for Mandani Bay really stemmed from our personal dreams and personal experiences. How come when you travel in different countries, you see fantastic developments where it’s always a fantastic experience to walk around in, where traffic and parking are not an issue? Everywhere that you go, everything is so orderly. That’s what we wanted to have here in Cebu,” shares Taft Properties’ COO Cristopher Narciso.</blockquote>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://media.philstar.com/images/the-philippine-star/lifestyle/modern-living/20160702/bayside-2B.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   Taft Properties COO Christopher Narciso, Hongkong Land CEO Robert Wong, Taft Properties chairman Jack Gaisano, Mandani Bay project director Gilbert Ang, and chief representative of Hongkong Land in the Philippines Finn Carew make up the minds and muscle behind the Philippines’ most ambitious waterfront community project.
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

<blockquote>“Some of these features are, in fact, pioneering in the Philippines. The usual issue of traffic within a township development, we’ve addressed that. We have two levels of vehicular traffic flow, three levels of pedestrian traffic flow, and you will see that the sub-ground levels of the whole 20 hectares of the development are interconnected to service all the parking requirements and vehicular traffic within,” Narciso notes. </blockquote>
<p>
  The efficiency of multiple traffic flows and refreshing bayside living can be gauged when the project’s first phase, the 1,200-unit residential complex, Mandani Bay Blue Seas, reaches completion by the year 2020. And plots for its studios, one-bedroom, two-bedroom and two-bedroom loft, city or bay-view properties—priced from 3 million to 20 million pesos—are selling fast.

</p>
<blockquote>“We saw that most of the market activities we have so far are from Cebu and from the Visayas. I think in the next phase, we plan to go internationally. Maybe it’s more for overseas Filipino workers, some buyers from Metro Manila as well. We see that the reception has been excellent for our value proposition. It’s a world-class development for a very affordable price,” shares Carew.</blockquote>
<p>Yet, with seven other residential phases and two more commercial phases to go, the developers at Mandani Bay made sure that no one is too early to pitch tent. “One thing that’s unique about our master plan, when you look at it being completed as a whole, we picture it to be an evolution. So, as we progress and build by phases the master plan will have interim components and features. We started with our interim green zone across, and by next year, we will have an interim retail strip, as well as interim office spaces. We assure that the lifestyle, the flavor, and the whole development can be initially experienced already,” explains Narciso.</p>

<p>Of the Mandani Bay’s 20 percent retail component, Carew adds that, “a lot of the retail will be at the podium level because we want to encourage street-level interaction and not too much of the boxed-up mall activity.” Add this with airy boardwalks, modern resort amenities, and a total of one-hectare dedicated to green areas, you have the formula for a mindful, mix-use of live, work, shop, and play right by the picturesque bay. </p>

<blockquote>“What this development really celebrates is its waterfront nature, built around water in a way that you can’t see in other developments in the Philippines. We’ve really done well with our waterfront developments around the world and we really want to bring this here,” Hong Kong Land’s Finn Carew asserts.

</blockquote>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://www.philstar.com/modern-living/2016/07/02/1598523/bayside-living-breaks-new-ground-mandani-bay"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandani Bay celebrates Cebu’s culture and creativity</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-08-27-philstar-mandani-bay-celebrates-cebus-culture-and-creativity/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-08-27-philstar-mandani-bay-celebrates-cebus-culture-and-creativity/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>Soon to join the iconic waterfront destinations such as the Thames River in London, Manhattan in New York, the Sydney Harbour in Australia, Marina Bay in Singapore, Victoria Harbour in...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-08-27-philstar-mandani-bay-celebrates-cebus-culture-and-creativity/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Mandani Bay celebrates Cebu’s culture and creativity</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/landing/hero.jpg" />
        <figcaption>video/mov</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:00:10 +08">2016-11-01 17:00:10 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
  Soon to join the iconic waterfront destinations such as the  Thames River in London, Manhattan in New York, the Sydney Harbour in Australia,  Marina Bay in Singapore, Victoria Harbour in Hong Kong, is Mactan Cebu’s  Mandani Bay.
</p>
<p>
The 20-hectare waterfront development, a joint venture of Hong Kong Land and Taft Properties, was recently launched in an affair that celebrated Cebuano culture and creativity while giving guests a glimpse of the world-class lifestyle destination that will put Cebu on the global map. </p>

<p>The ceremony started with the traditional ribbon cutting led by chief representative of Hong Kong Land in the Philippines Finn Carew, Taft Properties chief operating officer Christopher Narciso, Taft Properties chairman Jack Gaisano, Hong Kong Land executive director Robert Wong,  Mandaue City Mayor Luigi Quisumbing, Mandaue City Vice Mayor Carlo Fortuna and Cebu Vice Governor elect Agnes Magpale. Also in attendance were Cebu 6th District Congressman elect Jonas Cortes and Cordova Mayor Adelino Sitoy. The recently crowned Miss Mandaue 2016 Malka Shaver and second runner-up Luzenne Jones also attended the event.
</p>
<p>
The program featured  award-winning Cebuano performers such as the multi-awarded Mandaue Children’s Choir, the Cebu Classic Youth Orchestra,  the University of Cebu Dance Company and versatile soprano  Windey Prado  culminating   with a fabulous fireworks display.
</p>

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://media.philstar.com/images/the-philippine-star/lifestyle/modern-living/20160827/Mandani-Bay-Taft-Properties-COO-3.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   Taft Properties COO Christopher Narciso, CEO of Hong Kong Land, Robert Wong, Taft Properties chairman Jack Gaisano, Mandani Bay project director Gilbert Ang and Hong Kong Land chief representative in the Philippines Finn Carew
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://www.philstar.com:8080/modern-living/2016/08/27/1617503/mandani-bay-celebrates-cebus-culture-and-creativity"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/master-plan"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taft Properties, Hong Kong Land eye P130B microtownship in Cebu</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-25-cnnph-mandani-bay-taft-properties-hong-kong-land-mandaue-city-cebu/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-25-cnnph-mandani-bay-taft-properties-hong-kong-land-mandaue-city-cebu/index.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>The joint venture will build a mixed-use development of high rise residential, office, commercial and retail establishments on a 20-hectare property along the Mactan Channel which will be called Mandani...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/ia/newspaper/2016-05-25-cnnph-mandani-bay-taft-properties-hong-kong-land-mandaue-city-cebu/index.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>Taft Properties, Hong Kong Land eye P130B microtownship in Cebu</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="http://cnnphilippines.com/incoming/vvwdwa-Mandani-Bay_3_CNNPH.png/alternates/FREE_768/Mandani-Bay_3_CNNPH.png" />
        <figcaption>Mandani Bay</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 17:00:10 +08">2016-11-01 17:00:10 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    <p>
   The joint venture will build a mixed-use development of high rise residential, office, commercial and retail establishments on a 20-hectare property along the Mactan Channel which will be called Mandani Bay, Taft Properties COO Cristopher Narciso told reporters Thursday (May 19).


</p>
<p>
Taft Properties is backed by Vicsal Development Corp., the company behind the Metro Gaisano chain of stores.
 </p>
 <p>According to the latest (July 2015) figures from Philippine Statistics Authority, the Central Visayas economy grew by 8.8 percent in 2014. The growth rate is higher than the national average of 6.1 percent. Cebu accounts for a major portion of the region’s economy.</p>
 <blockquote>"We strongly feel that the residential demand here in Cebu will remain robust among different market segments," Narciso said. He cited the province's future developments, such as the Cebu-Cordova bridge and plans for a bus rapid transit (BRT) system navigating Metropolitan Cebu, which are expected to further enhance growth.</blockquote>

 <p>Hong Kong Land representative Finn Carew said his company’s joint venture with “a very strong Cebuano partner who knows this market and local tastes so well” is a “very powerful” combination.</p>

<p>Mandani Bay will feature a 500 meter-long waterfront along the Mactan Channel, Carew said.</p>

<p>Narciso said they obtained the services of the group responsible for authoring the environmental sustainability master plan of Vancouver, Canada, in planning the Mandani Bay, plus a traffic consultant to integrate the development to Mandaue City and Cebu City.


</p>

  <figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="http://cnnphilippines.com/incoming/mhe2r5-Mandani-Bay_1_CNNPH.png/ALTERNATES/FREE_720/Mandani-Bay_1_CNNPH.png"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>
<p>The plans also include support for future public ferries at the marina that will be built, Narciso said.
  
</p>
<p>Hong Kong Land has a 40 percent stake in the joint venture, the constitutional limit for foreign companies in such a project. It will take 15 years to complete the development.</p>


<p>Carew said the "vast majority" of buyers are from Cebu and the rest of the Visayas, but they are planning to market the development outside the region and among overseas Filipinos.
</p>

 <ul class="op-related-articles" title="Original Article">
    <li><a href="http://cnnphilippines.com/business/2016/05/25/mandani-bay-taft-properties-hong-kong-land-mandaue-city-cebu.html"></a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/"></a></li>
  </ul>



                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LIVE YOUR PASSION</title>
        <link>https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/blog/2016/05/welcome-to-mandani.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/blog/2016/05/welcome-to-mandani.html</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <author></author>
        
          <description>Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac,...</description>
        
        <content:encoded>
            <![CDATA[
                <!doctype html>
                <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
              <head>
                <meta charset="utf-8">
                <meta property="fb:pages" content="171758572945221" />
                
                <meta property="og:image" content="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/master-plan.jpg" />
                
                <link rel="canonical" href="https://www.cebuhomepages.com/l/mandani/blog/2016/05/welcome-to-mandani.html">
                <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                <meta property="fb:article_style" content="CHP Theme">
              </head>
              <body>
                <article>
                  <header>
                      <h1>LIVE YOUR PASSION</h1>
                      

      <!-- The cover image shown inside your article --> 
      <figure>
        <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/marina-1.jpg" />
        <figcaption>The Marina</figcaption>
      </figure>

      
                      <time class="op-published" dateTime="2016-10-29 17:00:00 +08">Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:00:00 +0800</time>
                      <time class="op-modified" dateTime="2016-11-01 18:00:00 +08">2016-11-01 18:00:00 +0800</time>
                  </header>
                  
                    Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.

Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. [Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor][Curabitur]. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Cras justo odio, dapibus ac facilisis in, egestas eget quam. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.

> Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Donec ullamcorper nulla non metus auctor fringilla. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.

Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus.

<figure data-feedback="fb:likes, fb:comments">
    <img src="https://dmcagfio3mnht.cloudfront.net/canvas/images/l/mandani/mbs.jpg"/>
    <figcaption class="op-small">
   <h1 class="op-large">Twin Towers of Mandani Bay Suites</h1> 
   eatures studio to three-bedroom units, and a number of individually designed special units including townhouses, lofts, penthouses, and garden units.
    <cite>passion is for adventure, culture, creativity, or water, live it at the Mandani Bay Suites.</cite> </figcaption>
 </figure>

Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Cras justo odio, dapibus ac facilisis in, egestas eget quam. [Nullam quis risus eget urna][nullam] mollis ornare vel eu leo. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet.

Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.

Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Cras justo odio, dapibus ac facilisis in, egestas eget quam. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.

[nullam]: #
[Curabitur]: #
                  
                    <footer>
                        <aside>
                            
                            We believe in Simplified Real Estate Transactions, Sound and Well Informed Decisions. Here to help. </aside>
                        <small>© cebuhomepages.com</small>
                  </footer>
                  <figure class="op-tracker">
    <iframe>
        <script>
        (function(i,s,o,g,r,a,m){i['GoogleAnalyticsObject']=r;i[r]=i[r]||function(){
          (i[r].q=i[r].q||[]).push(arguments)},i[r].l=1*new Date();a=s.createElement(o),
          m=s.getElementsByTagName(o)[0];a.async=1;a.src=g;m.parentNode.insertBefore(a,m)
        })(window,document,'script','https://www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js','ga');

        ga('create', 'UA-48709253-1', 'auto');
        ga('send', 'pageview');
      </script>
    </iframe>
                </article>
              </body>
            </html>
        ]]>
        </content:encoded>

      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>